[
	{
		"front": "... won its first World Cup in 1998.",
		"back": "France"
	},
	{
		"front": "... famously headbutted an opponent in the 2006 World Cup.",
		"back": "Zidane"
	},
	{
		"front": "... is the rivalry game played between Liverpool FC and Everton FC.",
		"back": "The Merseyside Derby"
	},
	{
		"front": "... has won the most World Cup trophies.",
		"back": "Brazil"
	},
	{
		"front": "... said, 'Maybe they hate me because I'm too good?'",
		"back": "Ronaldo"
	},
	{
		"front": "... is the highest division of professional soccer in the United States?",
		"back": "Major League Soccer"
	},
	{
		"front": "... yellow cards constitute an ejection of a player from the game.",
		"back": "2"
	},
	{
		"front": "... has scored the most international goals in soccer.",
		"back": "Abby Wambach"
	},
	{
		"front": "... is the highest-scoring male player in U.S. international soccer.",
		"back": "Landon Donovan"
	},
	{
		"front": "... is the name of world football's highest individual prize.",
		"back": "Ballon D'or"
	}
]